[{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980311540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":10832,"timeElapsed":85909},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980322595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":11051,"timeElapsed":96965},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980334170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":11572,"timeElapsed":108540},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980348114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":13940,"timeElapsed":122484},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980355298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":7180,"timeElapsed":129668},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980363946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":8644,"timeElapsed":138316},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980370978,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":7028,"timeElapsed":145347},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980385346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":14363,"timeElapsed":159715},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980399689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":14340,"timeElapsed":174059},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980413705,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":11116,"timeElapsed":188075},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980429001,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":15292,"timeElapsed":203371},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980434225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":5220,"timeElapsed":208595},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980445785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":11556,"timeElapsed":220155},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980455679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":9891,"timeElapsed":230049},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980464784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":9101,"timeElapsed":239153},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980470519,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5731,"timeElapsed":244889},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980480343,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":9821,"timeElapsed":254713},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980488847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":8500,"timeElapsed":263217},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980500103,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":8893,"timeElapsed":274472},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4277,"timeElapsed":278753},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980515313,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10925,"timeElapsed":289682},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980520360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":5043,"timeElapsed":294729},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980532399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":12037,"timeElapsed":306769},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980539999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7597,"timeElapsed":314369},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980547496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":7493,"timeElapsed":321866},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980555959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":8460,"timeElapsed":330329},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":14725,"timeElapsed":345057},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980575439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4748,"timeElapsed":349808},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980583007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6013,"timeElapsed":357376},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980589919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":6909,"timeElapsed":364288},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980595959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":6036,"timeElapsed":370328},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980608750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":12787,"timeElapsed":383120},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980613663,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4909,"timeElapsed":388033},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980619831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":6164,"timeElapsed":394201},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980629542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":9706,"timeElapsed":403912},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980636406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":6860,"timeElapsed":410776},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980641886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":5476,"timeElapsed":416256},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980649990,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8099,"timeElapsed":424360},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980661110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":6693,"timeElapsed":435479},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980668710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":7596,"timeElapsed":443080},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980672694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3980,"timeElapsed":447063},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980677013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":4316,"timeElapsed":451383},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980683494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":6476,"timeElapsed":457863},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980689542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":6044,"timeElapsed":463911},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980694117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":4571,"timeElapsed":468487},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980699733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":5613,"timeElapsed":474103},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980705157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":5419,"timeElapsed":479527},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980716661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":8516,"timeElapsed":491031},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980720117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3452,"timeElapsed":494487},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980726181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":6060,"timeElapsed":500551},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980733365,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":7180,"timeElapsed":507735},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980739093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":5724,"timeElapsed":513463},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980744220,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5123,"timeElapsed":518590},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980748164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3941,"timeElapsed":522534},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980753548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5381,"timeElapsed":527918},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980758164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4613,"timeElapsed":532534},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980771188,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":10573,"timeElapsed":545558},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980774932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3740,"timeElapsed":549302},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980783436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":8500,"timeElapsed":557806},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980791292,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":7852,"timeElapsed":565662},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980800196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":8899,"timeElapsed":574566},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980804740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4541,"timeElapsed":579110},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980810964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6221,"timeElapsed":585334},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980818771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":7804,"timeElapsed":593141},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980823427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4652,"timeElapsed":597797},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980838027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":12325,"timeElapsed":612397},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980842067,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4035,"timeElapsed":616437},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980847195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":5124,"timeElapsed":621565},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980872451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":25251,"timeElapsed":646821},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980884961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":12508,"timeElapsed":659331},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980889737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4772,"timeElapsed":664107},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980897553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":7812,"timeElapsed":671923},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980906657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":9100,"timeElapsed":681027},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980910873,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4212,"timeElapsed":685243},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980918609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":5652,"timeElapsed":692979},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980922689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4076,"timeElapsed":697059},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980927288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":4595,"timeElapsed":701658},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980932473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":5181,"timeElapsed":706842},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980937296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":4820,"timeElapsed":711666},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980944825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":7525,"timeElapsed":719195},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980949129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":4300,"timeElapsed":723498},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980955232,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6100,"timeElapsed":729602},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980959521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4284,"timeElapsed":733890},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980967401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5229,"timeElapsed":741770},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980972304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4899,"timeElapsed":746674},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980977864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":5557,"timeElapsed":752234},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980983232,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":5365,"timeElapsed":757602},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980987152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":3917,"timeElapsed":761522},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980993696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6540,"timeElapsed":768066},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980997760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":4060,"timeElapsed":772130},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981002313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4548,"timeElapsed":776683},{"subjectID":"2u0yyzl3by","prolificID":"6730f2e20f5915ff4ad2c07d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259d23951af88fd8c31","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981007705,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5388,"timeElapsed":782075}]